module.exports = [
  // below is the one object i have created whose structure should be followed
  {
    id: 0, // optional
    question: "What color is Master Yoda's lightsaber in the Star Wars films?",
    options: ["Green", "Pink", "Red", "Blue"],
    correct: "Green",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 1, // optional
    question:
      "According to Yoda, the ultimate Jedi advice is “Do. Or do not. There is no try.” But which of the following statements were not uttered by the Jedi Master?",
    options: [
      "“Judge me by my size, do you?”",
      "“That is why you win.”",
      "“A Jedi's strength flows from the Force.”",
      "“That is why you win.”",
    ],
    correct: "“That is why you win.”",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 2, // optional
    question:
      "Can you name the actor who plays Darth Vader in the Star Wars movies?",
    options: ["David Prowse", "Harrison Ford", "Oscar Isaac", "John Boyega"], // store options in an array
    correct: "David Prowse",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 3, // optional
    question: "Name the teen heartthrob who played the role of Cedric Diggory.",
    options: [
      "Robert Pattinson",
      "Rupert Grint",
      "Daniel RadCliffe",
      "Tom Felton",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Robert Pattinson",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 4, // optional
    question:
      " Can you remember which spell causes the tip of a wand to light up?",
    options: ["Lumos", "Nox", "Protego", "Imperio"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Lumos",
    hint: "Related to Light's Synonym", // optional
    fact: "You should try saying lumos to ur phone's assistant and watch", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 5, // optional
    question: " How many staircases does Hogwarts have?",
    options: ["142", "300", "210", "70"], // store options in an array
    correct: "142",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "These aren't your average, stationary stairs either. Each has a mind of its own, meaning they move at different speeds, change destinations on certain days, and sometimes even vanish entirely!", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 6, // optional
    question:
      "Which type of dragon does Viktor Krum face in the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    options: [
      "Hungarian Horntail",
      " Chinese Fireball",
      "Swedish Short-Snout",
      "Common Welsh Green",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Chinese Fireball",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "The Hungarian Horntail is the most dangerous of the four dragons.", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 7, // optional
    question: "Figure Out The Anagram: Herd Thresh Kit",
    options: [
      "Monsters, Inc.",
      "The Incredible Hulk",
      "Shrek the Third",
      "The Green Mile",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Shrek the Third",
    hint: "The Third Green Monster", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 8, // optional
    question: "Figure Out The Anagram: These Sex Hints",
    options: [
      "The Sense of an Ending",
      "The Sixth Sense",
      "Senseless",
      "Sense and Sensibility",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "The Sixth Sense",
    hint: "Cole Sear", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 9, // optional
    question: "Figure Out The Anagram: On One Male ",
    options: [
      "Home Alone",
      "Kevin and Perry Go Large",
      "My Left Foot",
      "American Beauty",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Home Alone",
    hint: "Kevin", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 10, // optional
    question:
      "Which film series from the 2000s stars Tom Cruise as Ethan Hunt?",
    options: [
      "James Bond: Casino Royale",
      "Mission: Impossible",
      "The Bourne Identity",
      "Die Hard: Mission Impossible",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Mission: Impossible",
    hint: "This film series features high-stakes espionage missions led by a skilled agent named Ethan Hunt.", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 11, // optional
    question: "Who played Sharkboy in Sharkboy and Lavagirl?",
    options: ["Taylor Lautner", "Zac Efron", "Jake Gyllenhaal", "Shia LaBeouf"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Taylor Lautner",
    hint: "He's known for his role as a werewolf in another popular film series", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 12, // optional
    question:
      "Which Disney movie starred Zac Efron as a high school basketball player?",
    options: [
      "High School Musical",
      "Teen Beach Movie",
      "High School Musical 2",
      "High School Musical 3:",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "High School Musical",
    hint: "This movie features a group of students who come together to perform in a musical", // optional
    fact: 'This movie launched Zac Efron\'s career as a teen heartthrob and features iconic songs like "Breaking Free" and "We\'re All in This Together', // optional
  },
  {
    id: 13, // optional
    question:
      " Name the animated movie in which a rat becomes a professional chef with the help of a human.",
    options: [
      "The Tale of Despereaux",
      "Flushed Away",
      "Stuart Little",
      "Ratatouille",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Ratatouille",
    hint: "This Pixar film is set in Paris and follows the culinary adventures of a rat named Remy", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 14, // optional
    question:
      "In the animated film, The Jungle Book, who says, “The bare necessities of life will come to you”?",
    options: ["King Louie", "Bagheera", "Baloo", "Raksha"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Baloo",
    hint: ' This character sings the song "The Bare Necessities," which features the famous line "The bare necessities of life will come to you', // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
];
